peachd.com 2019-03-11

# Peach Privacy Policy

Peach Privacy Policy
LAST REVISED ON: May 5th, 2016
This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes how your personal information is collected, used, and
disclosed by Peach Labs, Inc. and its related companies (“Peach” or “We” or “Us”). This
Policy applies to the Peach websites available at www.peachd.com or any of our other websites
that post this Policy (the “Site”) and our online services (the “Services”). This Policy does not
apply to websites that post different statements.
WHAT WE COLLECT
We collect information about you in a range of ways.
Information You Give Us.
We collect any personal information you provide to us. For example, you may provide us your
name, email address, phone number, delivery location, diet preferences, username, password,
and other information you directly give us using the Service.
If you tell us where you are (e.g., by allowing your device to send us your location), we may
store and use that information to provide you with location-based information.
If you place orders on our Site, we will collect all information necessary to complete the
transaction, including your name, credit card information, billing information and shipping
information. This information may be shared with third parties who help process and fulfill your
purchases.
Information Automatically Collected.
We automatically collect information about you and your computer or mobile device when you
visit our Site or use our Services. For example, we may log your computer or device operating
system type, location data, IP address, browser type, browser language, the website you visited
before browsing to our Site, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, access times, and
information about your use of and actions on our Site or in our Services.
        Cookies. We may automatically collect information using "cookies." Cookies are small
        data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us
        make our Site and your experience better. We use cookies to see which parts and features
        of our Site are popular and to count visits to our Site.
        Web Beacons. We may log information using digital images called “web beacons” (also
        called “pixel tags”) on our Site or in our emails. We use web beacons to manage cookies,
        count visits, and to learn what marketing works and what does not. We also use web
        beacons to tell if you open or act on our emails.

        Analytics. We use analytics services (including, but not limited to, Google Analytics) to
        help analyze how users use the Site. These analytics services use cookies, web beacons,
        and other technological methods to collect and store information such as how often users
        visit the Site, what features they use, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used
        prior to coming to the Site. We use the information we get from analytics services to
        improve our Site and our Services. Please see the following links for more information
        about Google Analytics and to opt: http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/
        and https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
INFORMATION COLLECTED BY PAYMENT PROCESSOR
When you make payments on our Site, our third party payment processor will collect all
information necessary to complete the transaction, including your name, credit card number and
billing address. When you transmit your payment information to our third party payment
processor, the personal information you upload, including your credit card number, name, and
address will be transmitted to our payment processor in an encrypted format via Secure Sockets
Layer (SSL) technology.
SOCIAL NETWORKING CONNECTIONS
If you choose to log on or otherwise associate the Services with another social networking site
account (e.g. Facebook), we may receive information from that social networking site to make it
easier for you to create an account on the Services and show our relevant content to you. Any
information that we collect from your other social networking service accounts may depend on
the privacy settings you have with that social networking service, so please consult the social
networking service’s privacy and data practices.
Some features of our Services may enable you to post content to social networking services. If
you choose to do this, we will provide information to such social networking services in
accordance with your elections. You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for
your use of those websites and that it is your responsibility to review the terms of use and
privacy policy of each applicable social networking service.
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We use personal information collected through our Services, or disclosed by you on our Site or
in connection with our Services, for the purposes described in this Policy. For example, we may
use your information to:
     •  operate, maintain, and improve our Site and Services;
     •  fill orders you place on the Site and Services;
     •  understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience and enjoyment using
        our Sites and Services;
     •  respond to comments and questions and provide customer service;
     •  send you related information including confirmations, updates, security alerts, and
        support and administrative messages (whether to your email address or via SMS text

        message in accordance with our Messaging Terms of Service available at
        https://www.peachd.com/sms_terms);
    •   communicate about promotions, upcoming events, and other news about Services offered
        by us and our partners;
    •   protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity;
    •   link or combine with other personal information we get from third parties, to help
        understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
    •   provide and deliver products and services that our customers request.
SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We do not share your personal information other than as follows:
    •   at your request, with restaurants that fill your orders;
    •   with delivery location representatives (e.g. office receptionist) who need access to your
        name and what you ordered so that your order can be fulfilled;
    •   with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work for us and
        need access to your information to do that work;
    •   to comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process;
    •   to protect the rights and property of Peach, our agents, users, and others including to
        enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of use;
    •   in an emergency to protect the personal safety of its users or any person;
    •   in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition,
        bankruptcy, dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture or
        disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets to another company.
We may create, use, and disclose de-identified and aggregated data for any purpose.
INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES
You may “opt-out” of receiving our promotional emails by following the instructions in those
emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-marketing emails. Non-marketing emails
include emails about your accounts and our business dealings with you.
You may send requests about your personal information to our contact information below. You
may request to change your contact preferences and update your personal information.
When you visit our Site, we and others give you the following choices about use of mechanisms
for tracking, including tracking of your online activities over time and across different websites
and online services by third parties. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If
you prefer, you can typically remove and reject cookies from our Site with your browser settings.
If you remove or reject our cookies, it could affect how our Site and Services work for you. You
can choose to opt-out of use of cookies by certain third-party analytics providers and advertising
networks to deliver ads tailored to your profile and preferences. You mean learn more about the
Google Analytics opt out here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. If you delete your
cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out

choice. While we and others give you choices described in this Policy, there are many ways web
browser signals and other similar mechanisms can indicate your choice to disable tracking, and
we may not be aware of or honor every mechanism.
CONTACT INFORMATION
We welcome your comments or questions about this Policy. Feel free to email us at
hello@peachd.com. You may also contact us at our address:
Peach Labs, Inc.
1201 3rd Ave, Ste 1500
Seattle, WA 98101
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will
change the Last Revised date above.
